Guide to the Stephen Tell Collection of Performing Arts Events at Duke, 1987-2001 UA.29.02.0223
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Stephen Tell Collection of Performing Arts Events at Duke
1987-2001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Tell, Stephen
UA.29.02.0223
4.5 Linear Feet
Collection contains video recordings of performing arts events at Duke from 1987-2001. The performances are largely Hoof'n'Horn but also include performances from the Dept. of Theater Studies, namely Duke Players.
85 Items
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research. However, reference copies must be made first.
Provenance
The Stephen Tell Collection of Performing Arts Events at Duke were received by the University Archives as a gift in 2009.
Collection Overview
Stephen Tell is a Duke alum hired by groups to create recordings of performing arts events. His collection includes video recordings of such events at Duke from 1987-2001, mostly of Hoof'n'Horn productions but it also includes performances by the Dept. of Theater Studies. Formats include VHS, SVHS, Umatic, and DVD.
Related Material
Hoof 'n' Horn Records
Duke University Archives
Summer Theater at Duke Records
Duke University Archives
Arts at Duke Reference Collection
Duke University Archives
Duke University. Hoof 'n' Horn; Duke University -- Students; Duke University. Duke Players; Duke University. Department of Theater Studies
- Audiocassettes (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, West Side Story, Act I (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, West Side Story, Act II (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, West Side Story, Act II Master (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, West Side Story, Act I parts 1-2 Master (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, West Side Story, Master, 1990 Oct. 21 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Man of La Mancha (from video), 1990 Winter (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Cabaret, parts 1-2, 1991 Jan. 18 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Cabaret, part 3, 1991 Jan. 18 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Cabaret, Act I, parts 1-2, 1991 Jan. 25 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Cabaret, Act II, 1991 Jan. 25 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Sweet Charity, part 1, 1989 May 13 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Sweet Charity, part 2, 1989 May 13 (Box 1)
  - Clef Hangers, 1986 (Box 1)
- Videocassettes
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Assassins, Edited Master, 1992 Oct. 29 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Assassins, tape 1 of 2, Raw Camera Master, 1992, Jan. 29 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Assassins, printed label and program insert, 1992 Oct. 29 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Baby, Act I (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Baby, Act II (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Baby, Edited Master, 1997 Jan. 31 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Cabaret, Master 2 T-30 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn/Duke Players, Carousel, Edited Master, 1996 Nov. 8 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn/Duke Players, Carousel, Act I, Camera Original, 1996 Nov. 8 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn/Duke Players, Carousel, Act II, Camera Original, 1996 Nov. 8 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, The Fanstasticks, Camera Original, 2000 Jan. 29 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Godspell, Act II (tape 2 of 2), camera backup feed, 1993 Jan. 28 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Guys and Dolls, Act I, Camera Original, 1997 Apr. 26 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Guys and Dolls, Act II, Camera Original, 1997 Apr. 26 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Guys and Dolls, Edited Master, 1997 Apr. 26 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Into the Woods, Edited Master, 2000 Oct. (Box 1)
    - Digital preservation file (Digital-materials UA29020223-SET-0001, Video-file UA-29-02-0223-0001_ffv1.mkv)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Into the Woods, Edited Master (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Little Shop of Horrors, Camera Original, 1995 Jan. 27 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Tommy, Camera Original, 2001 Feb. 3 (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Tommy, Edited Master, 2001 Feb. 3 (Box 1)
- DVD
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1996 (transfer from SVHS) (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Into the Woods, 1994 (transfer from SVHS) (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, 1996 (transfer from SVHS) (Box 1)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Merrily We Roll Along, 1995 (transfer from SVHS) (Box 1)
  - Dream True, 1997 Apr. 27 (transfer from SVHS) (Box 1)
- Videocassette (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Grease, Act I, 1993 Apr. 22 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Grease, Act II, 1993 Apr. 22 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Grease, Edited Master (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Godspell, Act I, 1993 Jan. 28 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Godspell, Master, 1993 Jan. 28 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, City of Angels, Camera Original, 1999 May 14 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Damn Yankees, Master, tape 1, 1990 May 12 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Damn Yankees, Master, tape 2, 1990 May 12 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Syekul and Stuck, Camera Original, 1996 March 29 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Syekul and Stuck, Camera Original, 1996 March 30 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Syekul and Stuck, Student Written Musicals, Edited Master, 1996 March 30 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, A Chorus Line, Edited Master, 2000 Apr. 22 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, A Chorus Line, Camera Original, 2000 Apr. 22 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Sweet Charity, Camera Original, 1999 Oct. 22 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Pippin, Master, 1991 Apr. 19 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, Edited Master, 1996 Apr. 19 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, Raw Camera Original, 1996 Apr. 19 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Into the Woods, 1994 Oct. 27 (Box 2)
    - Digital preservation file (Digital-materials UA29020223-SET-0001, Video-file UA-29-02-0223-0002_ffv1.mkv)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Into the Woods, Camera Original, 2000 Oct. 28 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Into the Woods, Camera Original, 1994 Oct. 23 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, West Side Story, Master, 1990 Oct. 21 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Man of La Mancha, Master, 1990 Winter (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Cabaret, Master, 1991 Jan. 24 (Box 2)
    - Digital preservation file (Digital-materials UA29020223-SET-0001, Video-file cabaret_master_001.mov)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Hair, Act I, 1995 Apr. 15 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Hair, Act I, 1995 Apr. 21 (Box 2)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Hair, Act II, 1995 Apr. 21 (Box 2)
  - West Side Story, Raw Camera Master (Box 2)
  - A Chorus Line, Camera Master, 1992 Apr. 26 (Box 2)
  - Man of La Mancha, Part 1 (Box 2)
  - Man of La Mancha, Part 2 (Box 2)
  - Damn Yankees, 1999 May 10 (Box 2)
- Videocassettes (Box 3)
  - Duke Players, The Sound of a Voice, Edited Master, 1996 Dec. 7 (Box 3)
  - Duke Players, Dream True, duplicated from SVHS original, 1997 Apr. 27 (Box 3)
  - Duke Drama, One Act Plays, Camera Original, 1996 Dec. 7 (Box 3)
  - John Altieri, Solo Performance, Master (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Little Shop of Horrors, Edited Master, 1995 Jan. 27 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Baby, Edited Master, 1997 Jan. 31 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Hair, Edited Master, 1995 Apr. 21 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, A Chorus Line, Edited Master, 1992 Apr. 26 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, Raw Camera, 1996 Jan. 27 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, Edited Master, 1996 Jan. 27 (Box 3)
- 3/4" U-matic Format Videocassettes
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Baby, reel 1, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Baby, reel 2, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Baby, reel 3, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Hair, reel 1, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Hair, reel 2, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Hair, reel 3, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Trust Me, Student Written Musical, reel 1 (Box 3)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, Trust Me, Student Written Musical, reel 2 (Box 3)
  - One Tape, Content Unknown (Box 3)